Guide to the Greater Yellowstone Coalition records1984-2020
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- News Clippings, 1984-2018; 3; 38 boxes
  - Environmental--miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Fall River, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Farming, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Federal land management, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Ferrets, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Fires, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Fishing/fisheries, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Gallatin National Forest, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Game farms, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Glacier National Park, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Grand Teton National Park, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Grazing, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Grazing--Upper Ruby, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Greater Yellowstone Association of Conservation Districts, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Greater Yellowstone Tomorrow, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Greenhouse effect--Ozone, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - GYC news clipping copies, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Henry's Fork, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Hunting and outfitting, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Yellowstone geothermal features, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - YNP (Yellowstone National Park) concessionaires, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - YNP--Winter use (snowmobiles, etc.), 1992 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Federal Agencies -- United States Forest Service, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Federal Agencies -- U.S. National Park Service, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Federal Agencies -- Bureau of Land Management, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Federal Agencies -- Bureau of Land Management, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Federal Agencies -- U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - State Agencies -- Fish and Game -- Idaho, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - State Agencies -- Game and Fish -- Wyoming, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - State Agencies -- Fish, Wildlife, and Parks -- Montana, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Jackson Hole development, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Jackson Hole Airport, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Land purchases, leases, easement, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Land exchanges, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Medicine Wheel, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Lions/cougars, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Mining--General, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Mining Law of 1872, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Mining--East Boulder, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Mining--Emigrant Gulch, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Mining--Cooke City, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Mining--Stillwater, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Mining--General, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Multiple use--Wise use, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Oil and Gas, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Opposition groups, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Poaching, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Politicians, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Predators, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Public land management, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Public opinion, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Recreation--Motorized, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Rivers, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Rock hauling in Yellowtone National Park, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Salmon, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Shoshone National Forest, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Snake River, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Spotted owls, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Targhee National Forest, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Targhee Resort, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Teton Pass, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Timber--General, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Todd Wilkinson, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Tourism, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - User fees, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Waste management, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Waste--Nuclear (INEL), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Water quality/contamination, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Water rights/stream flows, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - West Yellowstone, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Wetlands and riparians, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Whistleblowers, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife management, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Wilderness--General, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Wilderness--Idaho, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Wilderness--Wyoming, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Wilderness--Montana, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Wilderness--Montana, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Wilderness--Montana, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Wilderness violations, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Wind farms, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Wolves, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Wolves, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Wolves, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Wolves, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Wolves, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Wolves, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Yellowstone National Park--Winter use, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Yellowstone National Park concessionaires, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - BLM (Bureau of Land Management), 1992 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - U.S. National Park Service, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Forest Service, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Idaho Fish and Game, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Wyoming Game and Fish, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Montana--Fish, WIldlife and Parks, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Bison, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Bison, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Bison, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Bison, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Bison, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Bison, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Bison, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Bison, 1996-2003 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Bison, 1996-2003 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Bison, 1996-2003 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Bison, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Elk, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Elk, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - National media on Yellowstone River, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - American rivers stuff, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Yellowstone River, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Livingston Enterprise (rivers and fish), 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Oil and gas drilling, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Trout Unlimited, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Livingston levee, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Native fish, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Yellowstone Cutthroat, 1999-2008 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Billings Gazette on fish/rivers, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Boulder River, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Bozeman Chronicle on fish/rivers, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Dredge mining, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Suction gold dredging Yellowstone River, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Exotic species, 1999-2008 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Floodplain management, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 1996-1997 floods, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - FWP (Fish, Wildlife and Parks), 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin River, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin County floodplain, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - East Gallatin, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - GTNP (Grand Teton National Park) fish stalking, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - GTNP (Grand Teton National Park) fisheries, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Hoback River, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - USFWS (U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service), 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Snake River RMP (Resource Management Plan), 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Snake River (Jackson Hole), 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Hydropower/FERC (Federal Energy Regulatory Commission) Projects, 1999-2008 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - (Science) published articles, 1999-2008 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Overflights, June 2000-July 2003 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Winter use, July 2000-October 2003 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Winter use, July 2000-October 2003 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Winter use, July 2000-October 2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - CWD (Chronic Wasting Disease), 2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - CWD (Chronic Wasting Disease), 2001 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 38, Box 1)
  - Coalbed methane, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Coalbed methane, Gallatin and Park Counties, Montana, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Coalbed methane, Gallatin and Park Counties, Montana, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Coalbed methane, Gallatin and Park Counties, Montana, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Coalbed methane, other areas, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Coalbed methane, other areas, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Coalbed methane, other areas, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Coalbed methane, other areas, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - ATV's (All-Terrain Vehicles), 2003 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Beaverhead National Forest, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Biodiversity, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Bison, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Bison, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - BLM (Bureau of Land Management), 2003 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Bridger-Teton National Forest, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Coalbed methane, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Coalbed methane, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Coalbed methane, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Coalbed methane, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Coalbed methane, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Concessionaires, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Custer National Forest, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Editorials by GYC, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Elk, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Environment, general, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Environment, general, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Environmental groups, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - EPA (Environmental Protection Agency), 2003 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Endangered Species Act, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Farming and ranching, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Fee hunting, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Fires, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Fires, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Fires, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Fires, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Fish, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Flooding, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Forest Service, general, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin National Forest, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin River, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Game farms, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Glacier National Park, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Grand Teton National Park, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Grazing, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Grizzly bears, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Grizzly bears, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - GYC articles, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Idaho National Engineering and Environmental Laboratory, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Jackson Hole development, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Land exchanges, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - MEPA (Montana Environmental Policy Act), 2003 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Mining, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Montana Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Montana legislature, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - National Park Service, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - National parks, general, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Oil and gas, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Oil and gas, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Planning, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Predators, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Private land, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Public lands, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Rivers, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Rivers, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Roads/roadless, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Shoshone National Forest, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - TImber/logging, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - TImber/logging, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Tourism, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Whirling disease, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Wilderness, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Winter use, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Winter use, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Winter use, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Wolves, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Wolves, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Wolves, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Watersheds, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Wildlife diseases, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Wildlife diseases, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Wildlife, general, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife, general, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife, general, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Wyoming Game and Fish, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Wyoming Game and Fish, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Yellowstone River, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Big Horn Sheep, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Mad cow disease, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Migration corridors, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Predators, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Private lands, 2004-2005 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Private lands, 2004-2005 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Public lands, 2004-2005 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Public lands, 2004-2005 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Rivers, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Roadless, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Roadless, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Shoshone National Forest, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Ski area, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Targhee National Forest, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Timber/logging, 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Timber/logging, 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Tourism, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Watersheds, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Whirling disease, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Wilderness, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Wildlife disease, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife disease, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife disease, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Wildlife, general, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Wildlife, general, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Winter use, 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Winter use, 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Winter use, 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Wolves, 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Wolves, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Wolves, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Wolves, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Wolves, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Wyoming Fish and Game, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Yellowstone River, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Yellowstone to Yukon Conservation Initiative, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Audiovisual, 1984-2011; 4; 2 boxes
  This series contains content produced by and about the Greater Yellowstone Coalition, including TV segments on issues the GYC worked on such as the New World Mine.
  - Compilation of GYC Slideshows, October 11 1994 (Box 53, Usb-flash-drive 1)
  - 2001 Backcountry Outings, 2000 (Box 53, Compact-disc 60)
  - Arch 100 years--Dedication, 2003 (Box 53, Compact-disc 61)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition: Celebrating 20 Years of Conservation Success, 2003 (Box 53, Dvd 10)
  - GYE Maps, January 7, 2004 (Box 53, Compact-disc 62)
  - GYC 3.1, June 2, 2006 (Box 53, Dvd 11)
  - GYC 3.1 Film for A.M., June 2, 2006 (Box 53, Dvd 12)
  - New World Mine Reclamation Tour, July 6, 2006 (Box 53, Compact-disc 63)
  - 25 Years: Protecting the land you love, 2008 (Box 53, Dvd 13-14)
  - Final slideshow, 25th Anniversary GYC, 2008 (Box 53, Dvd 15)
  - Jenni Lowe 25th Artwork, 2008 (Box 53, Dvd 16)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition YouTube videos, CB Productions, 2012 (Box 53, Dvd 17)
  - GYC Films for YouTube (Box 53, Dvd 18)
  - Community Connections to Yellowstone: A Presentation by the Greater Yellowstone Coalition (Box 53, Dvd 19)
  - GYC Map--Eco for scanning (Box 53, Compact-disc 64)
  - GYC Homeground Radio (Box 54, Compact-disc 68)
  - Greater Yellowstone: Wild, Healthy and Whole 1982-2012-Rick Reese (Box 54, Dvd 21-22)
  - GYC Interview, Brent Stewart (Box 53, Dvd 20)
  - Forest Watch layout-Jessica (PDF of a newsletter) (Box 54, Compact-disc 65)
  - Greater Yellowstone Area Map, January 10, 2005 (Box 54, Compact-disc 66)
  - Yellowstone Crossing-Erik Schultz, 2004 (Box 54, Compact-disc 67)
  - RU4YNP Commercial Greater Yellowstone Coalition Colorburn Productions (Box 54, Dvd 23)
  - Yellowstone Snowmobiles (DVCam) (Box 53, Microcassette 1)
  - The Last Great American Gold Heist (Envrionmental Implications, Interviews w GYC folks-Robert Redford, Jim Barrett, Interviews in Cook City, Other Montanans) (Box 53, Dvd 24)
  - Montana High Divide Maps October 2010. American Wildlands GIS Map (Box 53, Dvd 25)
  - 90 Second Naturalist-9Tracks. Paper inventory attached. (Box 53, Compact-disc 68)
  - 90 Second Naturalist-Piece on Snowmobiles in YNP Bears, etc. Audio (Box 53, Compact-disc 69)
  - President Clinton and the New World Mine Agreement, August 12, 1996 (Box 54, Vhs 6)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition 2 x :30 spots, June 4, 2001 (Box 53, Vhs 7)
  - Yellowstone Wolf Reintroduction Oral Histories. A Bob Landis film. October 11 2012. Mammoth, Wyoming (Box 53, Compact-disc 70)
  - Trapper's Point Working Group, Upper Green River Valley-A Question of Balance Powerpoint (Box 53, Dvd 26)
  - A Simple Plot. June 14, 2012. The Daily Show with John Stewart (Box 53, Dvd 27)
  - Hunting Wolves, Saving Wolves. Now on PBS. 2/26/2010, February 26, 2010 (Box 53, Dvd 28)
  - Chronic Wasting Disease Meeting Presentations. 2/12/2003-Chico Hot Springs Powerpoints, February 12, 2003 (Box 53, Dvd 29)
  - Wyoming Range-Too Special to Drill (Box 53, Dvd 30)
  - Expedition Grizzly-Grizzly Creek Films (GYC BOD Member Tom Winston) (Box 53, Dvd 31)
  - Jared David Rogerson Boomtown (Box 53, Dvd 32)
  - RU4YNP Commercial V2 (Box 53, Dvd 33)
  - Snowmobiles in Yellowstone 4/14/2002, April 14, 2002 (Box 54, Vhs 8)
  - World Heritage Committee-Mammoth, Wyoming September 8-11 1995 (Box 54, Vhs 9-14)
  - ABC News: March 25, 2002 Under Siege from Snowmobiles (Box 54, Vhs 15)
  - ABC Good Morning America: Louisa Wilcox debates Crown Butte's Alan Kirk, April 20, 1994 (Box 54, Vhs 16)
  - Gold Mining Near Yellowstone CBS News Sunday (Box 54, Vhs 17)
  - The New Gold Rush-ABC TV (Box 54, Vhs 18)
  - Lighthawk and Clearcuts, 1990 (Box 54, Vhs 19)
  - CNN-Parks in Peril, CBC-New World Mine, CBS-Gold mining near Yellowstone (Box 54, Vhs 20)
  - Undermining Yellowstone, Worldwide Film Experiment (Box 54, Vhs 21)
  - Buffalo Bull- Cold Mountain, Cold Rivers (Box 54, Vhs 22)
  - NBC/ABC/McNeil Leher-New Wrold Mine (Box 54, Vhs 23)
  - Crown Butte Resources LTD. "The New World Project-A Rich HIstory and Future" (Box 52, Vhs 24)
  - Slides (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Publications, 1984-2013; 5; 0.8 linear feet 3 boxes
  Contains reports and publications related to environmental concerns/developments in the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem. Also includes a mostly complete run of the GYC's quarterly newsletter.
  - Status of Fisheries and Aquatic Habitats in the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem-Robert Van Kirk (2 Copies), 1999 (Box 55)
  - Greater Yellowstone Today: The Great Bear (2 Copies), 1991 (Box 55)
  - Exploring Greater Yellowstone Volume 1 Number 1, Spring-Summer 2005 (Box 55)
  - Exploring Greater Yellowstone Volume 2 Number 1, Spring-Summer 2005 (Box 55)
  - A Biological Conservation Assessment for the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem Executive Summary (2 copies), July 2001 (Box 55)
  - Threats to Greater Yellowstone, 1984 (Box 55)
  - An Environmental Profile of the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem (Box 55)
  - Incentives for Conserving Open Lands in Greater Yellowstone (2 copies), 1998 (Box 55)
  - Environmental Setting of the Yellowstone River Basin, Montana, North Dakota, and Wyoming. Water-resources Investigations Report 98-4269 (Box 55)
  - Organic Compounds and Trace Elements in the Fish Tissue and Bed Sediment From Streams in the Yellowstone River Basin, Montana and Wyoming, 1998 Water Resources Investigations Report 00-4190 (Box 55)
  - Explore Greater Yellowstone Cody Country Map & Guide (2 copies) (Box 55)
  - Ecoaction newsletters (Box 55)
  - Management of the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem: An Annotated Biography, 1999 (Box 55)
  - Greater Yellowstone People (9 copies) (Box 55)
  - River At A Crossroads: Development in the 100-Year Floodplain of the South Fork Snake River (2 Copies) (Box 55)
  - Riparian Area Assessment and Amphibian Status in the Watersheds of the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem (Box 55)
  - Necklace or Noose? Development at the Doorsteps of America's Public Lands: How Planning Can Shape a Better Future (Box 55)
  - When CBM Comes to Your Community: A Citizen's handbook with tools and methods for regulating coalbed methane development using community land use planning (Box 55)
  - Greater Yellowstone Challenges, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Greater Yellowstone in Peril: The Threats of Climate Disruption (Box 55)
  - An Environmental Profile of the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem: Executive Summary (2 copies) (Box 55)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 1984-1989 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 1990-1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 1995-1997 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 2000-2001 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 2005-2007 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 2008-2009 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 2010-2011 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Greater Yellowstone Report, 2012-2013 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Maps and Poster (Folder-os 1)
    Includes 25th anniversary poster print, signed for MSU by artist Jenny Lowe. Three maps of the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem.
- Web Archive, 2019-2022; 7
  Archive of the GYC website